academictips.org 2014-12-22

# Privacy Policy Policy | AcademicTips.org

Home : Privacy Policy

Dear Friends! Thank you for visiting AcademicTips.org. Your privacy is very important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you visit this website, and how we safeguard your information.

We created this Privacy Policy to give you confidence as you visit and use the site. We will never sell or disclose your information to third parties.

1\. Blog Notifications

Our blogs have features to notify you of new blog posts and new comments. If you subscribe to any of those features, we collect your email address so that we can send you the notifications.

We do not sale or disclose your email address to third parties. Besides from new posts and comments notifications, we do not send you any other types of emails.

Unsubscribe: In the event you would like to unsubscribe, please follow the following instructions: 

\- Locate one of our notification emails  
\- Locate and click on the Manage Subscription link at the bottom  
\- Check our site, choose Unfollow then Save Changes

2\. Traffic Data

The IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

3\. Google Ads

This website uses Google advertisements. Google uses technology such as cookies and web beacons to collect information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL: http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

4\. Links to Other Websites

From time to time, we may provide links to other websites we do not own so you can learn more about the topics. We do not have control and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such websites.

5\. Your Consent

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of information by AcademicTips as specified above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect and how we use it.

_Last revision: March 28, 2013_

AcademicTips.org, since December 1999.
